http://1stoutsource.org/about-2/privacy-policy-roymoggblog/

disclaimer – 1stOutsource Research
Skip to content
MENU
MENU About Us1stOutsourcePrivacy PolicyRules for ContributionsLog InContactNews|BlogsLatest PostsBusiness NewsManagement PracticePsychologyOutsourcingEducationSociety and CultureLog InPast ArticlesServicesResources and ToolsSurveys&TestsLog InQ&A ForumsLog In
We protect your privacy
Disclaimer and privacy policyWe do not collect or store personal information from our visitors or clients on this website.Use of Cookies:Cookies are small files which many web sites transfer to your hard disk and can inform the web site what pages you visit, and your preferences. We use cookies, but only for Blog management all parts of our site can be accessed without cookies being enabled. We do use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website blogs. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice click on the link here: Advertising Policy GoogleHow we use informationWe use the information provided to help us understand how our web site and which features are used.How we share informationWe do not and will never sell or share your personal information with any third party. Other web sites may have links on our site and if you link to their sites, they may collect information. These sites are not within our control and are not covered by this privacy statement.SecurityAny data entered onto our website Blogs is always stored in encrypted form in a database. If in the future Credit card transactions for services are offered they will be issued with a digital certificate, ensuring that your data can only be read by our transaction system – as long as your browser shows its secure mode symbol (such as a key or closed lock) you will beprotected by our security systems.ChildrenChildren under 16 are not allowed to register or post to the blog.Copyright and Trade MarksAll materials on this web site are the copyright of 1stOutsource or are reproduced with permission from other copyright owners. All rights are reserved. The materials on this web site may be retrieved and downloaded solely for personal use. No materials may be copied, modified, published, broadcast or otherwise distributed without the prior written permission of 1stOutsource. 1stOutsource and/or any other names of products or services provided and referred to on this web site are either trademarks or registered trademarks of the site owner.Posts made to the Blogs are the personnal opinion of the creator of the post and are free to use, modify or syndicate with due attribution to the poster.Disclaimer1stOutsource makes no warranties or representations of any kind concerning the accuracy or suitability of any information contained on this web site for any purpose. All such information is provided “as is” and with specific disclaimer of any warranties of merchantability, fitness for purpose, title and/or non-infringement. We make no warranties or representations of any kind that the services provided by this web site will be uninterrupted , error-free or that the web site or the server that hosts the web site are free from viruses or other forms of harmful computer code. In no event shall 1stOutsource, its employees or agents be liable for any direct, indirect or consequential damages resulting from the use of this web site. This exclusion and limitation only applies to the extent permitted by law and is without prejudice to any express provisions to the contrary in any written licence or subscription agreement from us in respect of the use of any online service provided or procured via this web site. Share this:Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on WhatsApp (Opens in new window) Leave a Comment Cancel ReplyYou must be logged in to post a comment.This site uses Akismet to reduce spam. Learn how your comment data is processed.
Copyright © 2020 1stOutsource Research | Powered by Astra
